Guide to the Burton Hall Papers WAG.087
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Union Democracy Cases, 67652
  - Subseries D: Transportation, 377309
    - International Association of Machinists (IAM), 67868
      - Memorandum & Order, Joseph M. McLaughlin, DJ, Jan 27, 1984; Correspondence, Dec 10, 1984, 67876 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Amended Standard Referral Order, Jan 5, 1985; Correspondence, BH, May 22, 1985, 67875 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Plaintiffs' Statement under Rule 3(g), Je 4, 1985; Revised Pre-Trial Order, Oct 23, 1985, 67874 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, Dec 20, 1985; Petition for Permission to Appeal, Aug 1, 1986, 1985, 1986; 67873 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, BH Apr 29, 1987; Transcript, Deposition, Michael Warfield, pp. 1-120, Nov 16, 1987, 67872 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Transcript, M. Warfield, pp. 121-171, Nov 17, 1987; Correspondence, Dec 19, 1987, 67871 (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Order, David F. Jordon, U.S. Magistrate, Jan 25, 1988; Transcript, Carl Gordon, pp. 1-52 (Corrected), Nov 16, 1987, 1987, 1988; 67870 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Pre-Trial Scheduling Order, Mar 1, 1988; Correspondence, Plaintiffs to BH, 67869 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Subseries E: Entertainment, 377310
    - American Federation of Musicians (AFM), 67842
      - Clean Slate By-Laws, Resolutions, Campaign; Gurton, Al, Rothstein, Murray, Glasel, John et. al., Local 802, AFM; Minutes of By-laws Meeting; Court Order, May 11, 1964; Edited Transcript of By-laws Meeting, Je 1, 1964; Appeal, Gurton & Rothstein, May 18, 1964; Transcripts, By-laws Meetings, 67867 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Musicians Voice; Opposition Leaflets, Reports, Notes, Resolutions, undated; 67866 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Gurton, Al, Rothstein, Murray, et. al. v. Manuti, Al, President, & Arons, Max, Secretary, Local 802, AFM, 64 Civ. 1158; Order to Show Cause Apr 1964; Judicial Opinion, May 11, 1964, 67865 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Gurton, Al, et. al. v. Arons, Max, Local 802, AFM, 64 Civ. 2292 (Cross-Referenced with 64 Civ. 2291); Deposition, J. Glasel, July, 1964; Opinion, U.S.D.J. Tenney; Notice of Appeal Sept, 1964; Index, Oct, 1964, 67864 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Guarnaccia, Rudolph, Rothstein, Murray, et. al. v. Kenin, Herman, President, Ballard, Stanley, Secretary, et. al., AFM, 64 Civ. 2291; Complaint; Index to Consolidated Record on Appeal; Correspondence, undated; 67863 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Docket No. 29232 (2292/2291); Brief & Appendix for Appellees; Motion for Staying Election, Feb 11, 1965, 67862 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (Moved - See Folder 21), undated; 67861 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Rothstein, Murray, Gurton, Al, Glasel, John, Guarnaccia, Rudy, et. al. v. Manuti, Al, et. al., Local 802, AFM; 64 Civ. 890; Summons & Complaint, Mar 19, 1964; Motion to Reargue Apr 28, 1964; Supporting Memorandum, 67860 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Notice of Motion Restraining Defendants, Je 5, 1964; Judicial Order Je 19, 1964; Annotated Fact Sheet, "The False Messsiahs," Sept, 1964, 67859 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Manuti, Al v. Rothstein, Murray, Supreme Court of the State of New York; Fact Sheet, Messiahs," Sept, 1964; Summons & Complaint, Sept 28, 1964; Notice of Deposition, Nov 30, 1964., 67858 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Deposition, M. Rothstein, Feb 2, 1965; Stipulation for Discontinuance, Oct 7, 1965, 67857 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Rothstein, Murray v. Shapiro, Sol, et. al., Local 802 AFM; Musicians Voice - "Plaintiffs Demand for a Bill of Particulars," Jan 11, 1964, 67856 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Arons, Al v. Rothstein, Murray, 1964, 67855 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Carroll, Joseph, et. al. v. AFM & Local 802, AFM; U.S. Court of Appeals, Docket No. 30445-46; Judicial Decision, Jan 30, 1967; Law Reporter on Carroll; Depositions; Plaintiffs-Appellees, 67854 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Brittan, Risdon v. Arons, Max, Local 802, AFM; 69 Civ. 4369; By-Laws. 1969, 67853 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Glasel, John v. Arons, Max, Local 802, AFM; 70 Civ. 860; Index (Partial); Correspondence, Mar 10, 1964; Summons & Complaint, Mar 3, 1970; Answer, 1964, 1970; 67852 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Memoranda for Summary Judgment; Judicial Decision, C.B. Motley, July 7, 1970; Plaintiff's Pre-Trial Memorandum, 67851 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Defendant's Pre-Trial Memoranda; Trial Memoranda, undated; 67850 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Depositions, Defendants, Je 7, 1974; Stipulation, Dismissal, Jan 27, 1976, 1974, 1976; 67849 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Robert Greenfield v. Local 802, AFM; 71 Civ. 1923; Court Papers, Oct 10, 1969; Correspondence, R. Greenfield, Oct 28, 1971, 1923, 1971; 67848 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Stipulation & Notice to Take Depositions, Jan 1, 1972; Pre Trial Examination, Mar 3, 1972; Correspondence, 67847 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, BH; Trial Memorandum, Plaintiff; Case Discontinued, Oct 8, 1974, 67846 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Local 802 Orphan folder; Fabowitz, Milton v. Local 802, 1964; Janell, Carl - NLRB, 1966; Elkin, Leo - Radio City Music Hall, 1979, 1964-1979; 67844 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Rank & File Documents - Correspondence, Publications, Platform, Resolutions, 1958-1969, 67843 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Operators (IATSE), 67814
      - Feltington, Dennis v. IATSE, Local 306, 77 Civ. 4417; Index; LRRM Summary with 1987 Memorandum & Decision; Letter of Expulsion, Nov 8, 1977; Questions for the Trial Committee, 1977, 1987; 67841 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - NLRB Charge, Deposition, D. Feltington, Feb 11 1977; Police Report, Criminal Trespass, May 10, 1977; Trial Transcript, 67840 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Report of Executive Board, May 31, 1977; Motion for Preliminary Injunction, Sept, 1977;Answer, Defendants, 67839 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Summons, Sept 7 1977; Affidavits in Opposition to Motion for Preliminary injunction, 67838 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Stipulation, Sept 29 1977; Correspondence, Dec 28, 1977, 67837 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - Endorsement, Jan 10 1978, Deposition, D. Feltington, pp. 1- 189, Mar 20, 1978, 67836 (Box 19, Folder 32)
      - Deposition, D. Feltington, pp. 190-345, undated; 67835 (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - Plaintiff's Memorandum on Issue of Trial Committee's Bias; Deposition, Abraham Friedman, Deposition, Alex Popkin, May 19, 1978, 67834 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Deposition, D. Feltington, pp. 1-100, May 19, 1978, 67833 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Deposition, D. Feltington, pp. 101-175, May 19, 1978, 67832 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Deposition, D. Feltington, pp. 177-232, May 21, 1978, 67831 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Magistrate's PreTrial Order May 26 1978; Court Hearing; PreTrial Order Je 5 1978, 67830 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence July 7 1978; Affirmation Aug 1 1978, 67829 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Plaintiff on Demand for Jury Trial; Correspondence Dec 23 1978, 67828 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Voir Dire of Prospective Jurors; Notice of Motion Dec 21 1979, 67827 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Docket No. 78-7583 Feltington; Court Papers, Jan 2, 1979; Court OrderJuly 18 1979; Order to Show Cause, July 23, 1979, 67826 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Affidavit (D. Feltington), July 23, 1979; Court Order, Aug, 1979, 67825 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Petition for Leave to Appeal; Petition for Rehearing; Correspondence, Feb 22, 1980, 67824 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Court Appearance before Judge Goettel, Feb 22, 1980; Notice of Appeal, Mar 25, 1980, 67823 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Notice of Motion, Mar 31, 1980; Correspondence (with Attachment) Jan 5, 1983, 1980, 1983; 67822 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Appellate Briefs; Petition for ReHearing, undated; 67821 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Joint Appendix (78-7583), undated; 67820 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Docket No. 80-7261 Appellate Briefs; Joint Appendix, undated; 67819 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - 85 Civ. 0303; Correspondence (BH) Apr 7 1987; Notice of Cross- Motion, Je 30, 1987, 67818 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - 77 Civ. 4417 / 85 Civ. 0303; Correspondence, July 6, 1987; Correspondence, Jan 2, 1990, 1987, 1990; 67817 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Constitution, By-Laws, Local 306; Trial Transcript; Removal from Union Office (with Map), undated; 67816 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Fine v Feltington, Picket Line Assault Charges, 1972-1975, 67815 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET), 67794
      - Plimack, H. v. NABET & Local 16 (& ABC), 84 Civ 0142 (LBS), (U.S.D.J. Leonard B. Sands) Arbitration Opinion and Award, Aug 3, 1983; Summons and Complaint; Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Preliminary Injunction (BH), 67813 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Plaintiff's Memorandum in Opposition to Defendant's Motion for Summary Judgment; Order - Judge Sands; Correspondence, Apr 4, 1984, 67812 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - 85 Civ. 4668 (LBS) Plimack (Continuance); Complaint (2nd), Je 14, 1985; Plaintiff's 1st Interrogatories, Dec 9, 1985, 67811 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Affidavit, H. Plimack Jan 6, 1984, 67810 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Deposition, J. Nolan, President, Local 16, Feb 5, 1986, pp. 1- 118, 67809 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Deposition, J. Nolan, pp. 119-223, undated; 67808 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Deposition, J. Nolan, pp. 224-290, Feb 12, 1986, 67807 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Deposition, J. Nolan, pp. 291-355; Deposition of W. Lloyd, pp. 1-46, Feb 28, 1986 (with Attachments), 67806 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Deposition, H. Plimack,; pp. 1-186A, Mar 18, 1986, 67805 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Apr 21, 1986; Affidavit, Howard Atlas, Region 1 Vice-President, NABET, Oct 30, 1986, 67804 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Notice of Motion for Defendants' Summary Judgment & Dismissing Plaintiff's Complaint, Nov 7, 1986; Reply & Answering Affidavit, J. Nolan, Dec 17, 1986, 67803 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Reply Affidavit, W. Sloan, Jan 14 1987; Decision, Judge Sands; Correspondence, W. Sloan, Apr 27, 1987, 67802 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits; Constitution, By-Laws Oct 14 1982, LM-2s, 67801 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits; Election Correspondence Oct 26 1978; "Dear NABET Brothers & Sisters," Aug 16, 1983, 1978, 1983; 67800 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits; Correspondence, Aug 18, 1983; Correspondence, Mar 12, 1985, 1983, 1985; 67799 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits; Trial Transcript, Dec 7, 1984; Correspondence, J. Nolan; Transcript (Select Pages), 67798 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Executive Board, Membership Meeting Minutes, with Notes, Dec 6, 1976 - Dec 19 1979, 1976-1979; 67797 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Executive Board, Membership Meeting Minutes, with Notes, Feb 13 1980 - Feb 28 1986, 1980-1986; 67796 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Undated Meeting Minutes, Notes, Correspondence, 67795 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Subseries F: Garment Workers - International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU), 67751
    - Putterman v. Knitgoods Workers; Local 155, ILGWU, 78 Civ. 6000 (MJL); Deposition, V. Putterman, pp. 1-118, Feb 21, 1979, 67793 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Deposition, V. Putterman, pp. 119-253, Feb 28, 1979, 67792 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Deposition, V. Putterman, pp. 254-386, Feb 28, 1979, 67791 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Deposition, Sol C. Chaikin, pp. 1-74, Sept 12, 1979, 67790 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Deposition, Sol Greene, pp. 1-82, Nov 12, 1979, 67789 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Deposition, Norman Lewis, pp. 1-41, Dec 5, 1979, Willard Aldrich, pp. 1-43, Dec 5, 1979, 67788 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Deposition, Salvatore De Angelis, pp. 1-169, Jan 8, 1980, 67787 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - The Cutters Independent Club; Proposals for Election Procedure, Jan 18, 1968; Correspondence, BH, Dec 18, 1968, 67786 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Complaint; Plaintiffs' Sur-Reply Memorandum, Jan 2, 1969; Plaintiff's Statement under Rule 9(g), Dec 20, 1969; Defendant's Reply Memorandum, Ravaschieri, Louis v. George P. Schultz, Secretary, Department of Labor (Failure to Enforce Title IV), 76 Civ. 3204, Dec 30, 1969, 67785 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Election Complaint, Jan 15, 1974; C.B. Motley, D.J., Memorandum & Opinion, 76 Civ. 3204, Mar 17, 1976, 1974, 1976; 67784 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Rosario, Tomas, Vega, Ovidio, & Cabel, Raymond v. Abe Dolgen, Manager, Local 10, & ILGWU, 69 Civ. 2958; Correspondence, T. Rosario to Local 10, Jan 21, 1970; Correspondence, BH, Aug 28, 1972, 1970, 1972; 67783 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Docket No. 76 - 7472, Rosario Appellees' Brief (BH), Defendants-Appellants' Brief, Oct 15, 1976, 67782 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Court Appearance, May 13 1977; Memorandum Opinion, C.B. Motley, pp. 1-60, Nov 14, 1977, 67781 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - 75 Civ. 4632 (CBM) / 75 Civ. 3204 (CBM); Deposition, T. Rosario,; pp. 1-150,Feb 13, 1978, 67780 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - 76 Civ. 3204 (CBM); Deposition, T. Rosario, pp. 151-301, undated; 67779 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Deposition, T. Rosario, pp. 302-542, undated; 67778 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Deposition, T. Rosario, pp. 1-112, Mar 8, 1970, 67777 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Pre-Trial examination, Vega, Ovidio, pp. 2-149, with Correspondence, undated; 67776 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Deposition, Cabel, Raymond E., pp. 1-186, Feb 21, 1978, 67775 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Pre-Trial Examination, R. Cabel, pp. 1-39, Mar 9, 1978; Pre-Trial Examination, Achu, Beraidin, pp. 1-37, Mar 31, 1978, 67774 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - 76 Civ. 3204 / 75 civ. 4632; Transcripts (Partial), undated; 67773 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - 78-7335; Appellate Briefs - Defendants, undated; 67772 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Appellate Brief - Plaintiffs; Petition for ReHearing (BH), undated; 67771 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - 78-7335-37; Reply Briefs of Defendant-Appellants, undated; 67770 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Joint Appendix, Vol. 1 of 2, undated; 67769 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Joint Appendix, Vol. 2; 78-7335-37, undated; 67768 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Petition for a Writ of Certiorari, Oct, 1979; Brief in Opposition, Local 10, 67767 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Deposition, B. Hall, Feb 1, 1982; 76 Civ. 3204, 67766 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - 75 Civ. 4632; Correspondence to Vincent P. Broderick, D.J., Je 6, 1983; Court Appearance, Transcript; Application for Fee Award, Apr 26, 1984, 1983, 1984; 67765 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - 84-7469 / 7491; Decision, U.S. Court of Appeals, Aug, 1984; Appellate Briefs; Reply Briefs; Joint Appendix, 67764 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Louis Mendola, Aronoff, Morris, Rodriquez, Pablo, Lascher, Jacob, Intra-union Charges, Local 10, NLRB, Correspondence, Aug 12, 1969; ILGWU Retirement Fund, Correspondence, Nov, 1978, 1969, 1978; 67763 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - David Spitzer, Local 10, Resolution on Legal Defense Fees for Abe Dolgen, LM-2, 1980, 67762 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Department of Labor/ILGWU, ILGWU Loans, 1971-1977, 67760 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - The Cutters Club Documents, Local 10 (Copies), undated; 67759 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Original Documents, Cutters Club, undated; 67758 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - F.O.U.R. / Chuck Lang, undated; 67756 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - F.O.U.R. Newsletters, News Articles on F.O.U.R., undated; 67755 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Original Papers on Staff Union Organizing, undated; 67754 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Industry Critiques/ILGWU; Newspaper & Magazine Clippings, "For the Record" - Justice; Response to NAACP; Reports, undated; 67753 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - ILGWU Documents (International), undated; 67752 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Subseries G: Hospital Workers - District 1199, National Union of Hospital & Health Care Employees - Retail, Wholesale, Department Store Union (RWDSU), 67717
    - Brown, Mattie v Nicholas, Henry, President, 82 Civ. 0913; Executive Board Meeting Minutes, Dec 5, 1981; Affidavit, B. Harper, Esq., Feb 18, 1982, 1981, 1982; 67750 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Deposition, Jerry Brown, Secretary-Treasurer, National Union, Feb 18, 1982; "1199 News," Feb, 1982, 67749 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Phillips, Russell v. Lenox Hill Hospital & District 1199, 86 Civ. 1026 (RWS); Grievances 1980-1981, 67748 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - NLRB Correspondence, Jan 3, 1984; Correspondence, R. Phillips 14-Mar-84, 67744 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - American Arbitration Ass. (AAA), Transcript, pp. 1-181, Mar 21, 1984, 67743 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - AAA Transcript, pp. 182-363, undated; 67742 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - AAA Transcript, pp. 364-544, Mar 21, 1984, 67741 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, R. Phillips, Mar 25, 1984; AAA Notice of Hearing, Oct 26, 1984, 67740 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, R. Phillips Jan 9 1985; Correspondence, R. Phillips Sept 18, 1985, 67739 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - 82 Civ. / 86 Civ. 1026 (RWS); NLRB Charge, R. Phillips, Jan 27, 1986; Correspondence, R.P. to BH, with NLRB Charges (Dismissals), 67738 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, R. Phillips to NLRB Apr 10, 1986; Correspondence from Defendant Hospital to Judge R.W. Sweet, Aug 5, 1986, 67737 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Note to B. Hall, Aug 17, 1986; AAA Opinion & Award, Dec 10, 1986, 67736 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Deposition, R. Phillips, pp. 1-184, Dec 10, 1986, 67735 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Defendant-Hospital's Request for Production, Dec 11, 1986; Deposition, R. Phillips, pp. 185-371, Dec 30, 1986, 67734 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Deposition & Subpoena, Andres Alfonso, Jan 7, 1987; Memorandum in Support of Hospital's Motion to Dismiss, Jan 20, 1987, 67733 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Deposition, R. Phillips, pp. 372-410, Jan 15, 1987; Deposition, with Corrections,Correspondence, Dec 9, 1986, 1986, 1987; 67732 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Hall to R.W. Sweet, Mar 23, 1987; Defendant Local 1199's 3(g) Statement of Facts, Mar 27 1987; Motion for Summary Judgment, 67731 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Affirmation with Exhibits, Mar 27, 1987, 67730 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Reply Memorandum in Support of Motion to Dismiss, Mar 30, 1987; Stipulation, Apr 29, 1987, 67729 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Affidavit, R. Phillips, pp. 1-42, with Exhibits, May 10, 1987, 67728 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Plaintiff's Memorandum in Opposition to 1199's Motion for Summary Judgment, May 12, 1987; Plaintiff's Rule 3 (g) Statements, May 13, 1987, 67727 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, July 8 1987; Amended Statement of Defendant 1199, 67726 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, BH, July 10, 1987; Settlement Stipulation, Feb 25, 1988, 1987, 1988; 67725 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - R. Phillips Employment Records, Notes, undated; 67723 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Notes (Undated), 67722 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Progressive Labor Party, Dec 19 1978; Flyers, Newsletters, Petitions, Nov., 1983; Undated Flyers, 1978, 1983; 67721 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Benin, Leigh, Vargas, Sam v. NYU Medical Center; NLRB Charge, Mar 24, 1972; NLRB Charge, Oct 11, 1979, 1972, 1979; 67720 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Puertas, Fred, 1199 / RWDSU v. NYU Medical Center; NLRB Charges 1982 -1983, 67718 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Subseries H: Unions (arrangement - alphabetical), 67653
    - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF STATE, COUNTY & MUNICIPAL EMPLOYEES (AFSCME). District Council 1707; 1964, 1980, 67715 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - AFSCME - District Council 37; PLP / INCAR (Committee Against Racism), 1983, 67714 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF TEACHERS (AFT); Zeluck, Steve; Executive Committee Meeting, Minutes, Nov 22 1968; Opinion & Order, Public Review Board, AFT, May 28 1971, 1968, 1971; 67713 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - UNITED FEDERATION OF TEACHERS (UFT); Loiacono, Charles, et. al., Arbitration Opinion & Award, NLRB Je 10 1971, 67712 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - BAKERY & CONFECTIONARY UNION; Deposition, BH Oct 16 1961; Joint Appendix, Gartner, Robert v. Soloner, Jack, President, Local 492, 67711 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Local 50 (Bakery); Correspondence, Jan 27 1983; Grievance, Lynn Bell, July 5, 1983, 67709 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - BRICKLAYERS, MASONS & PLUMBERS UNION, Local #1, undated; 67708 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - COMMUNICATION WORKERS OF AMERICA (CWA), Local 1101; Nabach, Joseph, Gilbert, Rusty, Kopp, Daniel v. New York Telephone Co. (Incomplete), undated; 67707 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - FEDERATION OF SPECIAL POLICE & LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICERS, 1981, 67706 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - HOTEL & RESTAURANT EMPLOYEES (HERE), Local 11, Chain Service; "Progress Bulletin," Local 11, Je 15, 1966; Complaint, Walgreen Eastern Co., Inc. v. James Gleason, Feb, 1966, 67705 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Local 11, Jan 2, 1968; Notice of Motion, Dec 18, 1968, 67704 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Preliminary Injunction; Correspondence, Je 25, 1969, 67703 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Appellee's Brief (BH, of Counsel); Memorandum in Support of Application to Intervene, undated; 67702 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Feb 15 1972; Plaintiff's Memorandum of Law, 67701 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Plaintiff's Answer to Interrogatories, Oct 17, 1972; Affidavit in Opposition to Application for Adjournment, 67700 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Fred Ferrara Protests, New Politics, (BH) Summer, 1967; Correspondence to G. Schultz, Department of Labor (Election Protest), Mar, 1969, 1967, 1969; 67699 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Local 11 Documents - Constitution, Flyers, Newsletters (Originals), undated; 67698 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - HERE Local 164, Bartenders - Plattdeutche v. Local 164; Flyer Nov 6 1963; NLRB Stipulation Feb 10, 1965, 1963, 1965; 67697 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - HERE Local 6 - U.S. Court of Appeals Decision 1967, W. Wirtz, Secretary, Department of Labor v. Local 6, 67696 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - HERE Local 6 - Raccioppi, Joan v. Marriott Food Service, et. al., NLRB; Correspondence, Mar 11, 1981; Order July 30 1981, 67695 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - HERE Local 6 - Friend, Irene v. Crowing Cock National Restaurants, 1981, 67694 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Delmonico's Restaurant - Hendrix, Sharon, NLRB, 1983, 67693 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - HERE Local 100 - In Re Trusteeship 1984, 67692 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - INDEPENDENT ASSOCIATION OF PUBLISHERS' EMPLOYEES (IAPE); Frankland, Eric; Index No. 18406 / 81, Supreme Court of State of New York; Statement Aug 24 1981; Reply Memorandum in Opposition to Petition, 67691 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Memorandum in Support of Motion; IAPE Note with Job Listings, 25-Sep-86, undated; 67690 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - INTERNATIONAL UNION OF ELECTRICAL WORKERS (IUE), Local 431, Genna, Guisseppe; NLRB 1983, 67688 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - INTERNATIONAL JEWELRY WORKERS UNION, Local No. 1; "Jewelry Worker Wildcats," Jan 20, 1972; Stipulation, Apr 3 1973, 1972, 1973; 67687 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - 73 Civ. 847 - (Jewelry); Memorandum in Opposition, Order for Judgment, July 16, 1973, 67686 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS ASSOCIATION (ALA); Local No. 1 - Lithographers; 73 Civ. 3056; Loekle, Robert & Pike, William v. Swayduck, Edward, President, Local No. 1; Deposition, R. Loekle, pp. 1-59, Mar 22 1976; Defendant's Post-Trial Brief, 75 Civ. 3056 (WK), Oct 19, 1976, 67685 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Chronology of 1980 Election; Note to BH, R. Loekle, with Attachments; Correspondence, Minutes, 67684 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, Dec 8, 1980; Meeting Transcript, pp. 1-58, Apr 1981, 1980, 1981; 67683 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Notice of Motion Sept 28 1981; Documents, 67681 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence & Stipulation, Oct 19, 1982; Answer, with Exhibits, Oct 27, 1982, 67680 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - 82 Civ. 6425 (RLC); Order, Robert L. Carter, D.J., Oct 26, 1982; Stipulation, Mar 22, 1984, 1982, 1984; 67679 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Lithographers - Grievance, Lalama, F., 1981, 67678 (Box 26, Folder 5)